Office of Publications Records UA012
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Faculty and Staff, 1960 -- 2002; 1963 -- 2002; UA012.003; 2.9 Linear Feet; 2 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains photographs, slides, and negatives of Tufts University faculty & staff from 1967 to 1999. It also contains the Office of Publications' files for individual employees, which include relevant press releases, resumes, and newspaper clippings. Aside from folders for individual staff members, this series also contains folders for offices, departments, and schools within Tufts.
  - Accreditation Committee, 1992; UA012.003.011.00001 (Box 11)
    Contains negative prints.
  - Admissions Office Personnel, 1976 -- 1992; UA012.003.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Alter, Judith B. - Liberal Arts / Dance, 1986; UA012.003.011.00003 (Box 11)
    Contains article about Judith Alter along with copy of her resume. Does not actually contain photographs.
  - Ampola, Dr. Mary, 1990; UA012.003.011.00004 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic print.
  - Anderson, Nancy - Faculty and Staff (present), 1980 -- 1993; UA012.003.011.00005 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints and negatives as well as material about Anderson's career at Tufts.
  - Anderson, Richard K. - Veterinary School, 1986; UA012.003.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Arnott - Drama, Dance, 1981; UA012.003.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Arts and Sciences photo shoot, 1997; UA012.003.011.00008 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints of unidentified students and faculty interacting in faculty offices.
  - Astill, Ken, 1980; UA012.003.011.00009 (Box 11)
    Date is approximate. Contains photographic print of Dean Astill, the Associate Dean of the College of Engineering.
  - Austin, John E. - Liberal Arts/Info. Tech, 1987 -- 1990; UA012.003.011.00010 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints and negative of Vice Provost "Jack" Austin. Also contains Austin's obituary.
  - Axelrod, Dr. Penny - Liberal Arts / Eliot Pearson, 1979 -- 1981; UA012.003.011.00011 (Box 11)
    Does not contain photographs, but information about Dr. Axelrod including resume and award letters.
  - Barrett, Peggy - Liberal Arts/Women's Programs, 1984 -- 1993; UA012.003.011.00012 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic print, newspaper article, and proposal for position of Coordinator of Women's Programs at Tufts.
  - Bernstein, Melvin - New Vice President, 1992 -- 1994; UA012.003.011.00013 (Box 11)
    Contains negatives, slides, and prints of Melvin Bernstein. Newspaper articles, biographies and resume are also included.
  - Bonsey, Rev. Steven - Chaplaincy, 1992; UA012.003.011.00014 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints.
  - Brown, J. Larry - Nutrition, 1989 -- 1999; UA012.003.011.00015 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints and documents pertaining to career of Larry Brown.
  - [BSOT Faculty], 1997; UA012.003.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds workers, 1984 -- 1986; UA012.003.011.00017 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints and negatives.
  - Campbell, Patricia - Dental School, 1996; UA012.003.011.00018 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints and article in the Dental Alumni Record about her position as executive associate dean.
  - Cath, Stanley - Medical School, 1979 -- 1983; UA012.003.011.00019 (Box 11)
    Contains no photographic prints, but contains articles and clippings about Cath's career.
  - Cebe, Peg, 1997; UA012.003.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - Chamberlain, Linda - Staff, 1994; UA012.003.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - Chamberlain, Linda - Staff, 1995; UA012.003.011.00022 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints of honorary degree recipient, Anson Chan, Chief Secretary of Hong Kong. Also contains a copy of her acceptance speech and a program from the awards ceremony where she received the honorary degree.
  - Cherniak, Christopher G., 1995; UA012.003.011.00023 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints and negatives as well as newspaper clippings and a copy of Cherniak's resume.
  - Cho, Dr. Sang I. - Medical School, 1984; UA012.003.011.00024 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic print and newspaper article about Dr. Marshall Kaplan and Dr. Sang Cho's liver transplant research.
  - Ciolfi, Sandra - Development/Alumni, 1986; UA012.003.011.00025 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic print and newspaper article about Alumni Secretary Sandra Ciolfi.
  - Clark, Veve - Liberal Arts / Romance Languages, 1983 -- 1987; UA012.003.011.00026 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints and newspaper articles.
  - Cleary, Roberta - Management / Sponsored Programs, 1984; UA012.003.011.00027 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic print and newspaper article.
  - Colcord, Frank C. - Liberal Arts / Fletcher, 1994; UA012.003.011.00028 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints and newspaper articles. Also contains Tufts University Proposal for the training of manpower managers.
    - Dean Frank Colcord, 1994; UA012.003.011.00028.00001; Morelli, Mark (Box 11)
      This image accompanied Frank Colcord's obituary in the July 2006 issue of Tufts Journal.
      Colcord, Frank C.
  - Cornish, Anthony - Drama, 1997; UA012.003.011.00029 (Box 11)
  - Cramer, Mary Jane - Liberal Arts / Soc., 1963 -- 1965; UA012.003.011.00030 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints and personnel record.
  - Cuttino, David - Liberal Arts / Admissions, 1986; UA012.003.011.00031 (Box 11)
    Contains resume and newspaper clipping. No photographic prints.
  - Dental School faculty, 1985 -- 1995; UA012.003.011.00032 (Box 11)
    Dates are approximate. Contains prints, negatives, and slides of various Dental School faculty members.
  - Eastwood, Mildred S. - Administration / Acad. Ser, 1975; UA012.003.011.00033 (Box 11)
    Contains no photographic prints. Contains resume and press release describing Eastwood's appointment into position of registrar.
  - Eastwood, William - Management / Financial Aid, 1967 -- 1987; UA012.003.011.00034 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints, resume and press releases.
  - Eaton, Elizabeth - Management / Health Sciences Library, 1986 -- 1997; UA012.003.011.00035 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints, film strips, and slides.
  - Eliot, Theodore L. - Fletcher School, 1980 -- 1985; UA012.003.011.00036 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints, newspaper clippings, press releases, and correspondence.
  - Engineering faculty, 1993 -- 1996; UA012.003.011.00037 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints and slides. Some depict generic faculty and student interactions and some are portraits of specific faculty members.
  - Evans, William J. - Medical School / HNRC, 1985 -- 1992; UA012.003.011.00038 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints, newspaper clippings, articles and resume of Prof. William "Bill" Evans.
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - deans, misc., 2001; UA012.003.011.00039 (Box 11)
    Contains slides and CD titled "Bacow Scans".
    - Bacow scans, 2001; UA012.003.011.00039.00001
  - Feldman, Lily Gardner - Liberal Arts / Poly-Sci, 1981 -- 1988; UA012.003.011.00040 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints, resume, newspaper clippings, and press release.
  - Fletcher, c. 1990-1996, UA012.003.011.00041 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints and negatives of Fletcher faculty and staff including Bernadette Kelly, Hurst Hannum, James L. Paddock, and many more. Also contains a number of photographs of foreign ambassadors and visitors to the Fletcher School.
  - Fletcher School faculty, 1986 -- 1997; UA012.003.011.00042 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints and negatives of Fletcher faculty and staff.
  - Flewelling, Rebecca S. - Management / Asst. Pres., 1986 -- 1997; UA012.003.011.00043 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints, negatives, and newspaper clippings.
  - Ford, Duane - Liberal Arts / Athletics, 1985 -- 1986; UA012.003.011.00044 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints and newspaper clippings of football coach Duane Ford.
  - Galo, Alvin Wright, 1997; UA012.003.011.00045 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints. Date is approximate.
  - Gordon, Bernard, 2000; UA012.003.011.00046 (Box 11)
    Contains a copy of the Tuftonian featuring Prof. Bernard Gordon.
  - GSAS photos, 2000; UA012.003.011.00047 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints of Graduate School professors including Linda Beardsley, Donna Wilson, Lisette Garcia, Carol Howard.
  - Hastings, David - Nutrition, 1995; UA012.003.011.00048 (Box 11)
  - Hollister, Rob, 1996; UA012.003.011.00049 (Box 11)
  - Hunt, Michael J - Liberal Arts / Chaplain, 1985 -- 1997; UA012.003.011.00050 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints and newspaper clippings.
  - Jacobs, Mary-Lee - Liberal Arts / Gen'l Consel, 1984; UA012.003.011.00051 (Box 11)
  - Kiely, Sally - Staff, 1993; UA012.003.011.00052 (Box 11)
  - Knabble, Bobbie, 1980; UA012.003.011.00053 (Box 11)
  - Knipp, Julian - Liberal Arts / Physics, 1987; UA012.003.011.00054 (Box 11)
    Contains newspaper clippings.
  - Lambert, Joseph J., 1974 -- 1996; UA012.003.011.00055 (Box 11)
  - Liberal Arts/Mathematics, George F. Leger, 1963 -- 1969; UA012.003.011.00056 (Box 11)
    Contains papers and newspaper clippings.
  - Library Staff, 1965 -- 1989; UA012.003.011.00057 (Box 11)
  - Medical School faculty [red], 1986 -- 1996; UA012.003.011.00058 (Box 11)
    Contains slides and negatives
  - Medina, Nadia (staff), 1996 -- 1999; UA012.003.011.00059 (Box 11)
    Contains photographic prints
  - Miller, Russell E., "Light on the Hill", 1966; UA012.003.011.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Museum (1 of 2), 1999; UA012.003.012.00001 (Box 12)
    Contains negative prints, photographs. Woman with Museum exhibits
  - Museum (2 of 2), 1999; UA012.003.012.00002 (Box 12)
    Contains negative prints, photographs. Man at Kennedy Library, handling exhibits
  - Nadelson, Carol, 1985 -- 1987; UA012.003.012.00003 (Box 12)
    Contains newspaper clippings, photograph.
  - Nickerson, Norton (Biology), 1963 -- 1987; UA012.003.012.00004 (Box 12)
    Contains newspaper clippings, photographs, papers
  - Dental School, dean Lonnie Norris [green], 1995; UA012.003.012.00005 (Box 12)
    Contains photographs, slides
  - Nutrition faculty A-D [purple], 1997; UA012.003.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - Nutrition faculty E-M [purple], 1986 -- 2002; UA012.003.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Nutrition faculty N-Z [purple], 1986 -- 1997; UA012.003.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - Nutrition faculty, misc [purple], 1985 -- 1995; UA012.003.012.00009 (Box 12)
    Contains photographs, slides. Date is approximate
  - Pederson, Marjorie, 1971 -- 1988; UA012.003.012.00010 (Box 12)
    Contains photographs, paper, newpaper clipings
  - Personell, 1983 -- 1987; UA012.003.012.00011 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic prints, slide
  - PT Eng 99 [1 of 2], 1995; UA012.003.012.00012 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic prints, negatives. Date is approximate
  - PT Eng 99 [2 of 2], 1995; UA012.003.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - PT Faculty 1999, 1995; UA012.003.012.00014 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic prints. Date is approximate
  - Rubin, Jeffrey [1 of 2], 1963 -- 1986; UA012.003.012.00015 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic prints, newspaper clippings, papers
  - Rubin, Jeffrey [2 of 2], 1981 -- 1986; UA012.003.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - Ryan, Hewson, 1986 -- 1991; UA012.003.012.00017 (Box 12)
  - Ryan, Richard M. Jr., 1990 -- 1992; UA012.003.012.00018 (Box 12)
  - Ryan, Daniel (Engineering), 1990; UA012.003.012.00019 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic print. Date is approximate
  - Sackler, faculty/admin [blue], 1995; UA012.003.012.00020 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic prints, slides. Date is approximate
  - Salem, Phil (Faculty and Staff), 1983 -- 1986; UA012.003.012.00021 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic prints, papers.
  - Santanewicz, Nancy (Faculty and Staff), 1981; UA012.003.012.00022 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic prints, papers, negatives.
  - Schneider, John(Faculty and Staff), 1994; UA012.003.012.00023 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic print
  - Spiegal, Harriet (Faculty and Staff), 1981 -- 1985; UA012.003.012.00024 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic prints, newspaper clippings
  - Staff, 1981 -- 1993; UA012.003.012.00025 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic prints, negatives
  - Storch, Rudolf F. (English), 1969; UA012.003.012.00026 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic prints, papers
  - Tufts Faculty and Staff 1980, UA012.003.012.00027 (Box 12)
  - Unger, Leonard, 1979 -- 1986; UA012.003.012.00028 (Box 12)
  - Vetenary School, faculty [pink], 1986 -- 1996; UA012.003.012.00029 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic prints, slides, negatives
  - Wolff, Sheldon M.D., 1983 -- 1987; UA012.003.012.00030 (Box 12)
  - Wren, Paul, 1990; UA012.003.012.00031 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic print, newspaper clipping
  - Zarker, John, 1981 -- 1989; UA012.003.012.00032 (Box 12)
  - Zeitlin, Marian F., 1981 -- 1993; UA012.003.012.00033 (Box 12)
    Contains photographic prints, papers, newspaper clippings
  - Arts and Science Faculty, 1995; UA012.003.013.00001 (Box 13)
    This folder contains negatives of professors, classrooms, discussion. Date is approximate
  - Chaplains, 1992; UA012.003.013.00002 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of the Chaplain around campus
  - Chemistry, 1997; UA012.003.013.00003 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of chemistry lab, professors
  - Chemistry and Archaelogy faculty scenes, 1990; UA012.003.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - A Cormack, dec. Nobel Lameate, 1990; UA012.003.013.00005 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of men around a computer, women studying. Date is approximate
  - A Cormack, 1990; UA012.003.013.00006 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of men around a computer. Date is approximate
  - A Cormack, 1990; UA012.003.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - A Cormack, 1990; UA012.003.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - A Cormack, 1990; UA012.003.013.00009 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of man with cannon and rendering. Date is approximate
  - Draper Lab, Ann Hynes, 1996; UA012.003.013.00010 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides woman in labratory.
  - Elkind, 1986 -- 1987; UA012.003.013.00011 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of man with children, group of adults, professor
  - Faculty, Carpenter - Stearns, 1961 -- 1962; UA012.003.013.00012 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of classroom scenes, library, professors
  - Faculty in action, 1986 -- 1987; UA012.003.013.00013 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of classroom scenes, chorus, academic quad, library roof, computer lab, professors
  - Faculty in classroom, 1966; UA012.003.013.00014 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of classroom scenes, professors
  - Faculty, media and library art, 1986; UA012.003.013.00015 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of classroom scenes, professors (with artwork and computers)
  - Gittelman, Sol, 1985; UA012.003.013.00016 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of classroom scenes, professors. Date is approximate
  - Hayopum, 1985; UA012.003.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Franettz Gopian, 1985; UA012.003.013.00018 (Box 13)
  - 46, 1996; UA012.003.013.00019 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of Rob Jacobs and eye technology
  - John Kreifeldt, 1995; UA012.003.013.00020 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of professor with technology. Date is approximate
  - liberal arts Faculty, 1986 -- 1987; UA012.003.013.00021 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of professors, classroom scenes
  - liberal arts Faculty, 1986 -- 1987; UA012.003.013.00022 (Box 13)
  - liberal arts Faculty, 1986 -- 1987; UA012.003.013.00023 (Box 13)
  - Library - Seth, 1988; UA012.003.013.00024 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of professor talking with students and colleagues, woman studying
  - Library - Seth (1989), 1988; UA012.003.013.00025 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of professors and students in the library, proffessor reading
  - Library - Seth (1989), 1988; UA012.003.013.00026 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of man on computer, students studying, reception desk, professors discussing
  - Medical Faculty, 1985; UA012.003.013.00027 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of professors discussing. Date is approximate
  - M. Morelli, Jayanthi Mistry, 1985; UA012.003.013.00028 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of professor teaching. Date is approximate
  - Music dept. (Karen), 1997; UA012.003.013.00029 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of woman with computers
  - Rotberg, 1987; UA012.003.013.00030 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of professor with computer, discussing, posing
  - Science Faculty, 1985; UA012.003.013.00031 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of students, outside class, faculty, professors posing. Date is approximate
  - Science Faculty, 1986 -- 1987; UA012.003.013.00032 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of sunset/Charmichael, Fletcher, students, classroom scenes, labratory scenes, computers, professors
  - Science Faculty, 1985; UA012.003.013.00033 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of professors, outside classes
  - Marc Morelli, Chris Swan, 1985; UA012.003.013.00034 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of professor with technology/lab set up. Date is approximate
  - Dean Toupin, Bobbie Knoble, 1981 -- 1985; UA012.003.013.00035 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of dean and student talking, classroom scenes, professors
  - Tufts professors, classes, 1960; UA012.003.013.00036 (Box 13)
  - Tufts professors, classes, 1960; UA012.003.013.00037 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of classroom scenes, conductor. Date is approximate
  - Unidentified, 1996; UA012.003.013.00038 (Box 13)
    This folder contains slides of professor.
- Subject Files, 1930 -- 2008; UA012.004; 9.9 Linear Feet; 6 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains photographs, slides, and negatives depicting identified Tufts events, departments, activities, and academic subjects. The subjects in this series might overlap with those found in other series, but the content differs. For example, folders labeled "Library" in subject files show students using the library and engaging in library-related activities, whereas those materials labeled "Library" in the Buildings & Grounds series show the physical structure of the library. This series contains a large number of photographs of annual Tufts events, including commencement photographs from 1952 to 2002, and images of Alumni Weekend, Mayoralty, Tuftonia's Day, and Homecoming. There are also photographs from one-time events, like the 1992 World's Fair and groundbreaking ceremonies for campus buildings. Academic subject areas like engineering, chemistry, and medicine also have strong representation. There are also images of select extracurricular activities like Yacht Club, orchestra, and dance.
  - Photo File: Tufts Tomorrow, 2002; UA012.004.006.00001 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Contains photographs of the event, along with event invitation and book of negatives from event.
  - Tufts Tomorrow Reception, 1996; UA012.004.006.00002 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Contains photographs of the event.
  - UEP - Summer School, 1994; UA012.004.006.00003 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Photo File - UN Day, 2001; UA012.004.006.00004 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Undergraduate Admissions, 1980; UA012.004.006.00005 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Veterinary School - animals (close up), 1986 -- 1995; UA012.004.006.00006 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Dates are approximate. This folder contains photographic prints, slides, and negatives of owls, llamas, dogs, cats, sheep and birds.
  - Vet School - Animal Expo, 1995; UA012.004.006.00007 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Veterinary School - Animals outside, 1986 -- 1995; UA012.004.006.00008 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Date is approximate. Includes photographic prints and slides. Some international shots depicting monkeys and camels, but mostly cows, horses, and sheep.
  - Veterinary School - Grafton, buildings, 1990; UA012.004.006.00009 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Includes photographs and slides of the Grafton Veterinary School campus. Includes architectural renderings.
    - Exterior view of Franklin M. Loew Veterinary Medical Education Center, 1990; UA012.004.006.00009.00001; Fertita, L. (Box UA012 Shared 2)
      Exterior views; slide (photograph); Webster Veterinary Library; School of Veterinary Medicine; Tufts University
    - [Paddock on the Cummings Veterinary School campus], 1990; UA012.004.006.00009.00002 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
      Exterior views; Pastures; slide (photograph); Tufts University; School of Veterinary Medicine
  - Veterinary School - Grafton [old], 1980 -- 1995; UA012.004.006.00010 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Includes photographs of the Grafton Veterinary School campus. Also some photographs of Circus Day event.
  - Veterinary School - people and animals, 1984 -- 1994; UA012.004.006.00011 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Includes photographs and slides.
  - Veterinary School - professors with students, 1990; UA012.004.006.00012 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Date is approximate. Includes photographic slides and negatives.
  - Veterinary School - vets doing exams, 1985 -- 1995; UA012.004.006.00013 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Date is approximate. Includes photographic slides, prints, and negatives.
  - Veterinary School - vets in surgery, 1983 -- 1986; UA012.004.006.00014 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Date is approximate. Includes photographic slides and prints.
  - Veterinary School - vets with animals (posed), 1983 -- 1995; UA012.004.006.00015 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
  - Veterinary School - vets with equipment, 1995; UA012.004.006.00016 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Date is approximate. Includes photographic prints and slides.
  - Veterinary School - vets with horses, 1986 -- 1995; UA012.004.006.00017 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Date is approximate. Includes photographic prints, negatives and slides.
  - Veterinary School - wildlife, 1991 -- 1996; UA012.004.006.00018 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Date is approximate. Includes photographs of vet students with various birds.
  - WMFO, 1986; UA012.004.006.00019 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Includes one photograph of student at radio station.
  - World Leadership Conference, 1990; UA012.004.006.00020 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Date is approximate. Photographs from the Hugh O'Brian Youth Foundation World Leadership Conference.
  - World's Fair, 1992; UA012.004.006.00021 (Box UA012 Shared 2)
    Includes photographs of students fencing and students singing karaoke.
  - Advising, 1995; UA012.004.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - Aidekman, 1991 -- 1993; UA012.004.014.00002 (Box 14)
    Contains photographic prints/negatives of art exhibts, construction of Aidekman
  - Alumni Leadership dinner, 1992; UA012.004.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - Alumni, 1956 -- 1990; UA012.004.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1986; UA012.004.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1989; UA012.004.014.00006 (Box 14)
    Contains photographic print of class of 1939
  - Alumni Weekend, 1991; UA012.004.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1992; UA012.004.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - Amalgamates, 1991; UA012.004.014.00009 (Box 14)
    Contains photographic print and photocopy
  - American Studies, 1996; UA012.004.014.00010 (Box 14)
    Contains course booklet and papers
  - Annual fund, 1970; UA012.004.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - Archival shots, 1983 -- 1988; UA012.004.014.00012 (Box 14)
    Contains photographic prints and negatives
  - Armenian Plaque, UA012.004.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Asbestos Info. Ctr., 1985 -- 1986; UA012.004.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - Asian Awareness Week, 1987; UA012.004.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - ATA Assoc. of Tufts Alumnae, 1991; UA012.004.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - Athletics (1 of 4) [green], 1991 -- 1992; UA012.004.014.00017 (Box 14)
    Contains photographic prints and slides
  - Athletics (2 of 4) [green], 1980 -- 1995; UA012.004.014.00018 (Box 14)
    Contains photographic prints and slides. Date is approximate
  - Athletics (3 of 4) [green], 1980 -- 1996; UA012.004.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Athletics (4 of 4) [green], 1981 -- 1988; UA012.004.014.00020 (Box 14)